(Raj:)That sounds amazing.
First movie I'm watching, Annie.
(Howard:)How exactly
would these glasses work?
(Jimmy:)How the hell should I know?
That's why I need a nerd.
(Leonard:)I don't think something
Iike that's even possible.
Aw, come on. You could figure it out.
You're, like, the smartest guy.
(Sheldon:)The smartest?... All right.
(Sheldon:)I may not have a firm grasp on sarcasm,
but, uh, even I know that was a doozy.
(Sheldon:)You can't live
in fear of this man forever.
- Sheldon, I got this.
- You clearly don't.
(Sheldon:)What my spineless friend
Iacks the courage to say...
(Sheldon:)...is you're a terrible person
who took advantage of his tiny size...
(Sheldon:)...his uncoordinated nature,
and his congenital lack of masculinity.
(Penny(entering):)- Sheldon.
- Leonard, I platonically love you, man.
(Sheldon:)But face it, you're a mess.
(Jimmy:)I don't understand.
(Leonard:)I think what he's trying to say
is that maybe...
(Leonard:)...in high school,
you picked on me a little bit.